# **JOSE CORTES**

BUSINESS DEVELOPER

+57 3167520083

② Josea2002.11@gmail.com

Carrera 19 #93-26, Bogota Colombia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-cortes-b13713249/

#### **ABOUT ME**

Web developer with a 3 plus years in business management and digital marketing, graduated from Coder House, Cámara de comercio de Bogota and Cesa. Proficient in programming languages including HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Experienced in developing responsive websites, and custom web applications for over 1 year and entrepreneurship leadership within have owned clothing brands. Possesses excellent communication, Leadership, code logic and organizational skills.

### **EDUCATION**

Cesa Coder House

Bachelor of Business Management Bachelor of Web development

2020 - 2024 2020 - 2021

### **EXPERTISE**

Management Skills

Digital Marketing

Negotiation

Critical Thinking

Communication Skills

Logical equations

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **CLothing brand**

2019 - Present

North Exhibition

- CEO and leader in North Exhibition
- Managed to sell 10 million pesos in 1 month
- Made some designs for the brand using illustrator
- Made the web page for the brand, with an ecommerce model

#### Web platform

Jan 2022 - Present

CLAPP inc

- CEO and leader in CLAPP inc
- Managed to finish a mockup platform in 2 months
- made all web designs for the platform
- Achieved welcoming 5 promoters for the platform

#### Yoga business

Dec 2020 - Present

Total Relax Yoga

- Owner and leader in Total Relax Yoga
- Manage to get sales up to 40 million pesos in 3 months
- Made the web page and platform in less than 4 months
- Leader of 5 workers
- Changed the business model to an E-platform

## **CERTIFICATION**

#### **Digital Marketing**

Camara de comercio de Bogota

2020 - 2021

Completed a course with the Camara de comercio de Bogota, and achieved a high level and a top 1 tier of the class

#### Front end

Front end simplified

2023 - 2023

Completed a course where achieved web develpment skills, and linkdin skills

## **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish (Native)
- English (C2)
- French (B1)

